<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><grammar xml:lang="en-US" root="index_37" tag-format="semantics/1.0" version="1.0" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2001/06/grammar"><rule id="index_37"><one-of><item>greenish<tag>out.annotation="";out.startIndex="37";</tag></item><item>greenish skin<tag>out.annotation="";out.startIndex="37";</tag></item><item>greenish skin he<tag>out.annotation="";out.startIndex="37";</tag></item><item>greenish skin he wore.<tag>out.annotation="";out.startIndex="37";</tag></item><item>greenish skin he wore. He<tag>out.annotation="";out.startIndex="37";</tag></item><item>greenish skin he wore. He longed<tag>out.annotation="action=scene_10;";out.startIndex="37";</tag></item><item>greenish skin he wore. He longed to<tag>out.annotation="action=scene_10;";out.startIndex="37";</tag></item><item>greenish skin he wore. He longed to be<tag>out.annotation="action=scene_10;";out.startIndex="37";</tag></item><item>greenish skin he wore. He longed to be a<tag>out.annotation="action=scene_10;";out.startIndex="37";</tag></item><item>greenish skin he wore. He longed to be a handsome<tag>out.annotation="action=scene_10;";out.startIndex="37";</tag></item><item>greenish skin he wore. He longed to be a handsome man,<tag>out.annotation="action=scene_10;";out.startIndex="37";</tag></item><item>greenish skin he wore. He longed to be a handsome man, to<tag>out.annotation="action=scene_10;action=scene_11;";out.startIndex="37";</tag></item><item>greenish skin he wore. He longed to be a handsome man, to win<tag>out.annotation="action=scene_10;action=scene_11;";out.startIndex="37";</tag></item><item>greenish skin he wore. He longed to be a handsome man, to win her<tag>out.annotation="action=scene_10;action=scene_11;action=scene_12;";out.startIndex="37";</tag></item><item>greenish skin he wore. He longed to be a handsome man, to win her heart<tag>out.annotation="action=scene_10;action=scene_11;action=scene_12;";out.startIndex="37";</tag></item><item>greenish skin he wore. He longed to be a handsome man, to win her heart and<tag>out.annotation="action=scene_10;action=scene_11;action=scene_12;";out.startIndex="37";</tag></item><item>greenish skin he wore. He longed to be a handsome man, to win her heart and hold<tag>out.annotation="action=scene_10;action=scene_11;action=scene_12;";out.startIndex="37";</tag></item><item>greenish skin he wore. He longed to be a handsome man, to win her heart and hold her<tag>out.annotation="action=scene_10;action=scene_11;action=scene_12;";out.startIndex="37";</tag></item><item>greenish skin he wore. He longed to be a handsome man, to win her heart and hold her hand.<tag>out.annotation="action=scene_10;action=scene_11;action=scene_12;";out.startIndex="37";</tag></item><item>greenish skin he wore. He longed to be a handsome man, to win her heart and hold her hand. But<tag>out.annotation="action=scene_10;action=scene_11;action=scene_12;action=scene_13;";out.startIndex="37";</tag></item><item>greenish skin he wore. He longed to be a handsome man, to win her heart and hold her hand. But froggy<tag>out.annotation="action=scene_10;action=scene_11;action=scene_12;action=scene_13;";out.startIndex="37";</tag></item><item>greenish skin he wore. He longed to be a handsome man, to win her heart and hold her hand. But froggy eyes<tag>out.annotation="action=scene_10;action=scene_11;action=scene_12;action=scene_13;";out.startIndex="37";</tag></item><item>greenish skin he wore. He longed to be a handsome man, to win her heart and hold her hand. But froggy eyes cried<tag>out.annotation="action=scene_10;action=scene_11;action=scene_12;action=scene_13;";out.startIndex="37";</tag></item><item>greenish skin he wore. He longed to be a handsome man, to win her heart and hold her hand. But froggy eyes cried froggy<tag>out.annotation="action=scene_10;action=scene_11;action=scene_12;action=scene_13;";out.startIndex="37";</tag></item><item>greenish skin he wore. He longed to be a handsome man, to win her heart and hold her hand. But froggy eyes cried froggy tears,<tag>out.annotation="action=scene_10;action=scene_11;action=scene_12;action=scene_13;";out.startIndex="37";</tag></item><item>greenish skin he wore. He longed to be a handsome man, to win her heart and hold her hand. But froggy eyes cried froggy tears, and<tag>out.annotation="action=scene_10;action=scene_11;action=scene_12;action=scene_13;";out.startIndex="37";</tag></item><item>greenish skin he wore. He longed to be a handsome man, to win her heart and hold her hand. But froggy eyes cried froggy tears, and misted<tag>out.annotation="action=scene_10;action=scene_11;action=scene_12;action=scene_13;";out.startIndex="37";</tag></item><item>greenish skin he wore. He longed to be a handsome man, to win her heart and hold her hand. But froggy eyes cried froggy tears, and misted up<tag>out.annotation="action=scene_10;action=scene_11;action=scene_12;action=scene_13;";out.startIndex="37";</tag></item><item>greenish skin he wore. He longed to be a handsome man, to win her heart and hold her hand. But froggy eyes cried froggy tears, and misted up his<tag>out.annotation="action=scene_10;action=scene_11;action=scene_12;action=scene_13;";out.startIndex="37";</tag></item><item>greenish skin he wore. He longed to be a handsome man, to win her heart and hold her hand. But froggy eyes cried froggy tears, and misted up his bright<tag>out.annotation="action=scene_10;action=scene_11;action=scene_12;action=scene_13;";out.startIndex="37";</tag></item></one-of></rule></grammar>