<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><grammar xml:lang="en-US" root="index_53" tag-format="semantics/1.0" version="1.0" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2001/06/grammar"><rule id="index_53"><one-of><item>needs<tag>out.annotation="";out.startIndex="53";</tag></item><item>needs you,<tag>out.annotation="";out.startIndex="53";</tag></item><item>needs you, Toni<tag>out.annotation="";out.startIndex="53";</tag></item><item>needs you, Toni dear,<tag>out.annotation="";out.startIndex="53";</tag></item><item>needs you, Toni dear, to<tag>out.annotation="";out.startIndex="53";</tag></item><item>needs you, Toni dear, to make<tag>out.annotation="";out.startIndex="53";</tag></item><item>needs you, Toni dear, to make him<tag>out.annotation="";out.startIndex="53";</tag></item><item>needs you, Toni dear, to make him smile<tag>out.annotation="";out.startIndex="53";</tag></item><item>needs you, Toni dear, to make him smile from<tag>out.annotation="";out.startIndex="53";</tag></item><item>needs you, Toni dear, to make him smile from ear<tag>out.annotation="";out.startIndex="53";</tag></item><item>needs you, Toni dear, to make him smile from ear to<tag>out.annotation="";out.startIndex="53";</tag></item><item>needs you, Toni dear, to make him smile from ear to ear.<tag>out.annotation="";out.startIndex="53";</tag></item><item>needs you, Toni dear, to make him smile from ear to ear. Kiss<tag>out.annotation="";out.startIndex="53";</tag></item><item>needs you, Toni dear, to make him smile from ear to ear. Kiss him<tag>out.annotation="";out.startIndex="53";</tag></item><item>needs you, Toni dear, to make him smile from ear to ear. Kiss him please<tag>out.annotation="";out.startIndex="53";</tag></item><item>needs you, Toni dear, to make him smile from ear to ear. Kiss him please and<tag>out.annotation="";out.startIndex="53";</tag></item><item>needs you, Toni dear, to make him smile from ear to ear. Kiss him please and do<tag>out.annotation="";out.startIndex="53";</tag></item><item>needs you, Toni dear, to make him smile from ear to ear. Kiss him please and do not<tag>out.annotation="";out.startIndex="53";</tag></item><item>needs you, Toni dear, to make him smile from ear to ear. Kiss him please and do not wince.<tag>out.annotation="";out.startIndex="53";</tag></item><item>needs you, Toni dear, to make him smile from ear to ear. Kiss him please and do not wince. Perhaps<tag>out.annotation="";out.startIndex="53";</tag></item><item>needs you, Toni dear, to make him smile from ear to ear. Kiss him please and do not wince. Perhaps this<tag>out.annotation="";out.startIndex="53";</tag></item><item>needs you, Toni dear, to make him smile from ear to ear. Kiss him please and do not wince. Perhaps this frog<tag>out.annotation="";out.startIndex="53";</tag></item><item>needs you, Toni dear, to make him smile from ear to ear. Kiss him please and do not wince. Perhaps this frog might<tag>out.annotation="";out.startIndex="53";</tag></item><item>needs you, Toni dear, to make him smile from ear to ear. Kiss him please and do not wince. Perhaps this frog might be<tag>out.annotation="";out.startIndex="53";</tag></item><item>needs you, Toni dear, to make him smile from ear to ear. Kiss him please and do not wince. Perhaps this frog might be a<tag>out.annotation="";out.startIndex="53";</tag></item><item>needs you, Toni dear, to make him smile from ear to ear. Kiss him please and do not wince. Perhaps this frog might be a prince.<tag>out.annotation="";out.startIndex="53";</tag></item></one-of></rule></grammar>