<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><grammar xml:lang="en-US" root="index_8" tag-format="semantics/1.0" version="1.0" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2001/06/grammar"><rule id="index_8"><one-of><item>foxes<tag>out.annotation="";out.startIndex="8";</tag></item><item>foxes howled<tag>out.annotation="";out.startIndex="8";</tag></item><item>foxes howled and<tag>out.annotation="";out.startIndex="8";</tag></item><item>foxes howled and called<tag>out.annotation="";out.startIndex="8";</tag></item><item>foxes howled and called him<tag>out.annotation="";out.startIndex="8";</tag></item><item>foxes howled and called him mad.<tag>out.annotation="";out.startIndex="8";</tag></item><item>foxes howled and called him mad. I<tag>out.annotation="action=scene_16;";out.startIndex="8";</tag></item><item>foxes howled and called him mad. I am<tag>out.annotation="action=scene_16;";out.startIndex="8";</tag></item><item>foxes howled and called him mad. I am not<tag>out.annotation="action=scene_16;";out.startIndex="8";</tag></item><item>foxes howled and called him mad. I am not mad,<tag>out.annotation="action=scene_16;";out.startIndex="8";</tag></item><item>foxes howled and called him mad. I am not mad, not<tag>out.annotation="action=scene_16;";out.startIndex="8";</tag></item><item>foxes howled and called him mad. I am not mad, not even<tag>out.annotation="action=scene_16;";out.startIndex="8";</tag></item><item>foxes howled and called him mad. I am not mad, not even funny.<tag>out.annotation="action=scene_16;";out.startIndex="8";</tag></item><item>foxes howled and called him mad. I am not mad, not even funny. You'll<tag>out.annotation="action=scene_16;action=scene_17;";out.startIndex="8";</tag></item><item>foxes howled and called him mad. I am not mad, not even funny. You'll see!<tag>out.annotation="action=scene_16;action=scene_17;";out.startIndex="8";</tag></item><item>foxes howled and called him mad. I am not mad, not even funny. You'll see! I'll<tag>out.annotation="action=scene_16;action=scene_17;";out.startIndex="8";</tag></item><item>foxes howled and called him mad. I am not mad, not even funny. You'll see! I'll ask<tag>out.annotation="action=scene_16;action=scene_17;action=scene_18;";out.startIndex="8";</tag></item><item>foxes howled and called him mad. I am not mad, not even funny. You'll see! I'll ask my<tag>out.annotation="action=scene_16;action=scene_17;action=scene_18;";out.startIndex="8";</tag></item><item>foxes howled and called him mad. I am not mad, not even funny. You'll see! I'll ask my old<tag>out.annotation="action=scene_16;action=scene_17;action=scene_18;";out.startIndex="8";</tag></item><item>foxes howled and called him mad. I am not mad, not even funny. You'll see! I'll ask my old friend<tag>out.annotation="action=scene_16;action=scene_17;action=scene_18;";out.startIndex="8";</tag></item><item>foxes howled and called him mad. I am not mad, not even funny. You'll see! I'll ask my old friend Bunny.<tag>out.annotation="action=scene_16;action=scene_17;action=scene_18;";out.startIndex="8";</tag></item><item>foxes howled and called him mad. I am not mad, not even funny. You'll see! I'll ask my old friend Bunny. Bunny<tag>out.annotation="action=scene_16;action=scene_17;action=scene_18;action=scene_19;";out.startIndex="8";</tag></item><item>foxes howled and called him mad. I am not mad, not even funny. You'll see! I'll ask my old friend Bunny. Bunny listened<tag>out.annotation="action=scene_16;action=scene_17;action=scene_18;action=scene_19;";out.startIndex="8";</tag></item><item>foxes howled and called him mad. I am not mad, not even funny. You'll see! I'll ask my old friend Bunny. Bunny listened very<tag>out.annotation="action=scene_16;action=scene_17;action=scene_18;action=scene_19;";out.startIndex="8";</tag></item><item>foxes howled and called him mad. I am not mad, not even funny. You'll see! I'll ask my old friend Bunny. Bunny listened very grave,<tag>out.annotation="action=scene_16;action=scene_17;action=scene_18;action=scene_19;";out.startIndex="8";</tag></item><item>foxes howled and called him mad. I am not mad, not even funny. You'll see! I'll ask my old friend Bunny. Bunny listened very grave, his<tag>out.annotation="action=scene_16;action=scene_17;action=scene_18;action=scene_19;";out.startIndex="8";</tag></item><item>foxes howled and called him mad. I am not mad, not even funny. You'll see! I'll ask my old friend Bunny. Bunny listened very grave, his whiskers<tag>out.annotation="action=scene_16;action=scene_17;action=scene_18;action=scene_19;";out.startIndex="8";</tag></item><item>foxes howled and called him mad. I am not mad, not even funny. You'll see! I'll ask my old friend Bunny. Bunny listened very grave, his whiskers twitched,<tag>out.annotation="action=scene_16;action=scene_17;action=scene_18;action=scene_19;";out.startIndex="8";</tag></item><item>foxes howled and called him mad. I am not mad, not even funny. You'll see! I'll ask my old friend Bunny. Bunny listened very grave, his whiskers twitched, his<tag>out.annotation="action=scene_16;action=scene_17;action=scene_18;action=scene_19;";out.startIndex="8";</tag></item><item>foxes howled and called him mad. I am not mad, not even funny. You'll see! I'll ask my old friend Bunny. Bunny listened very grave, his whiskers twitched, his tail<tag>out.annotation="action=scene_16;action=scene_17;action=scene_18;action=scene_19;";out.startIndex="8";</tag></item></one-of></rule></grammar>