<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><grammar xml:lang="en-US" root="index_17" tag-format="semantics/1.0" version="1.0" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2001/06/grammar"><rule id="index_17"><one-of><item>ruby<tag>out.annotate="";out.startIndex="17";</tag></item><item>ruby lips,<tag>out.annotate="";out.startIndex="17";</tag></item><item>ruby lips, a<tag>out.annotate="action=scene_25;";out.startIndex="17";</tag></item><item>ruby lips, a kiss<tag>out.annotate="action=scene_25;";out.startIndex="17";</tag></item><item>ruby lips, a kiss to<tag>out.annotate="action=scene_25;";out.startIndex="17";</tag></item><item>ruby lips, a kiss to launch<tag>out.annotate="action=scene_25;";out.startIndex="17";</tag></item><item>ruby lips, a kiss to launch a<tag>out.annotate="action=scene_25;";out.startIndex="17";</tag></item><item>ruby lips, a kiss to launch a thousand<tag>out.annotate="action=scene_25;";out.startIndex="17";</tag></item><item>ruby lips, a kiss to launch a thousand ships.<tag>out.annotate="action=scene_25;";out.startIndex="17";</tag></item><item>ruby lips, a kiss to launch a thousand ships. But<tag>out.annotate="action=scene_25;action=scene_26;";out.startIndex="17";</tag></item><item>ruby lips, a kiss to launch a thousand ships. But no<tag>out.annotate="action=scene_25;action=scene_26;";out.startIndex="17";</tag></item><item>ruby lips, a kiss to launch a thousand ships. But no great<tag>out.annotate="action=scene_25;action=scene_26;";out.startIndex="17";</tag></item><item>ruby lips, a kiss to launch a thousand ships. But no great transformation<tag>out.annotate="action=scene_25;action=scene_26;";out.startIndex="17";</tag></item><item>ruby lips, a kiss to launch a thousand ships. But no great transformation came.<tag>out.annotate="action=scene_25;action=scene_26;";out.startIndex="17";</tag></item><item>ruby lips, a kiss to launch a thousand ships. But no great transformation came. The<tag>out.annotate="action=scene_25;action=scene_26;action=scene_27;";out.startIndex="17";</tag></item><item>ruby lips, a kiss to launch a thousand ships. But no great transformation came. The frog<tag>out.annotate="action=scene_25;action=scene_26;action=scene_27;";out.startIndex="17";</tag></item><item>ruby lips, a kiss to launch a thousand ships. But no great transformation came. The frog ran<tag>out.annotate="action=scene_25;action=scene_26;action=scene_27;";out.startIndex="17";</tag></item><item>ruby lips, a kiss to launch a thousand ships. But no great transformation came. The frog ran off<tag>out.annotate="action=scene_25;action=scene_26;action=scene_27;";out.startIndex="17";</tag></item><item>ruby lips, a kiss to launch a thousand ships. But no great transformation came. The frog ran off to<tag>out.annotate="action=scene_25;action=scene_26;action=scene_27;";out.startIndex="17";</tag></item><item>ruby lips, a kiss to launch a thousand ships. But no great transformation came. The frog ran off to hide<tag>out.annotate="action=scene_25;action=scene_26;action=scene_27;";out.startIndex="17";</tag></item><item>ruby lips, a kiss to launch a thousand ships. But no great transformation came. The frog ran off to hide his<tag>out.annotate="action=scene_25;action=scene_26;action=scene_27;";out.startIndex="17";</tag></item><item>ruby lips, a kiss to launch a thousand ships. But no great transformation came. The frog ran off to hide his shame.<tag>out.annotate="action=scene_25;action=scene_26;action=scene_27;";out.startIndex="17";</tag></item><item>ruby lips, a kiss to launch a thousand ships. But no great transformation came. The frog ran off to hide his shame. Bunny<tag>out.annotate="action=scene_25;action=scene_26;action=scene_27;action=scene_28;";out.startIndex="17";</tag></item><item>ruby lips, a kiss to launch a thousand ships. But no great transformation came. The frog ran off to hide his shame. Bunny chased<tag>out.annotate="action=scene_25;action=scene_26;action=scene_27;action=scene_28;";out.startIndex="17";</tag></item><item>ruby lips, a kiss to launch a thousand ships. But no great transformation came. The frog ran off to hide his shame. Bunny chased in<tag>out.annotate="action=scene_25;action=scene_26;action=scene_27;action=scene_28;";out.startIndex="17";</tag></item><item>ruby lips, a kiss to launch a thousand ships. But no great transformation came. The frog ran off to hide his shame. Bunny chased in hot<tag>out.annotate="action=scene_25;action=scene_26;action=scene_27;action=scene_28;";out.startIndex="17";</tag></item><item>ruby lips, a kiss to launch a thousand ships. But no great transformation came. The frog ran off to hide his shame. Bunny chased in hot pursuit.<tag>out.annotate="action=scene_25;action=scene_26;action=scene_27;action=scene_28;";out.startIndex="17";</tag></item><item>ruby lips, a kiss to launch a thousand ships. But no great transformation came. The frog ran off to hide his shame. Bunny chased in hot pursuit. Don't<tag>out.annotate="action=scene_25;action=scene_26;action=scene_27;action=scene_28;";out.startIndex="17";</tag></item><item>ruby lips, a kiss to launch a thousand ships. But no great transformation came. The frog ran off to hide his shame. Bunny chased in hot pursuit. Don't be<tag>out.annotate="action=scene_25;action=scene_26;action=scene_27;action=scene_28;";out.startIndex="17";</tag></item><item>ruby lips, a kiss to launch a thousand ships. But no great transformation came. The frog ran off to hide his shame. Bunny chased in hot pursuit. Don't be an<tag>out.annotate="action=scene_25;action=scene_26;action=scene_27;action=scene_28;";out.startIndex="17";</tag></item></one-of></rule></grammar>