<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><grammar xml:lang="en-US" root="index_22" tag-format="semantics/1.0" version="1.0" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2001/06/grammar"><rule id="index_22"><one-of><item>launch<tag>out.annotate="";out.startIndex="22";</tag></item><item>launch a<tag>out.annotate="";out.startIndex="22";</tag></item><item>launch a thousand<tag>out.annotate="";out.startIndex="22";</tag></item><item>launch a thousand ships.<tag>out.annotate="";out.startIndex="22";</tag></item><item>launch a thousand ships. But<tag>out.annotate="action=scene_26;";out.startIndex="22";</tag></item><item>launch a thousand ships. But no<tag>out.annotate="action=scene_26;";out.startIndex="22";</tag></item><item>launch a thousand ships. But no great<tag>out.annotate="action=scene_26;";out.startIndex="22";</tag></item><item>launch a thousand ships. But no great transformation<tag>out.annotate="action=scene_26;";out.startIndex="22";</tag></item><item>launch a thousand ships. But no great transformation came.<tag>out.annotate="action=scene_26;";out.startIndex="22";</tag></item><item>launch a thousand ships. But no great transformation came. The<tag>out.annotate="action=scene_26;action=scene_27;";out.startIndex="22";</tag></item><item>launch a thousand ships. But no great transformation came. The frog<tag>out.annotate="action=scene_26;action=scene_27;";out.startIndex="22";</tag></item><item>launch a thousand ships. But no great transformation came. The frog ran<tag>out.annotate="action=scene_26;action=scene_27;";out.startIndex="22";</tag></item><item>launch a thousand ships. But no great transformation came. The frog ran off<tag>out.annotate="action=scene_26;action=scene_27;";out.startIndex="22";</tag></item><item>launch a thousand ships. But no great transformation came. The frog ran off to<tag>out.annotate="action=scene_26;action=scene_27;";out.startIndex="22";</tag></item><item>launch a thousand ships. But no great transformation came. The frog ran off to hide<tag>out.annotate="action=scene_26;action=scene_27;";out.startIndex="22";</tag></item><item>launch a thousand ships. But no great transformation came. The frog ran off to hide his<tag>out.annotate="action=scene_26;action=scene_27;";out.startIndex="22";</tag></item><item>launch a thousand ships. But no great transformation came. The frog ran off to hide his shame.<tag>out.annotate="action=scene_26;action=scene_27;";out.startIndex="22";</tag></item><item>launch a thousand ships. But no great transformation came. The frog ran off to hide his shame. Bunny<tag>out.annotate="action=scene_26;action=scene_27;action=scene_28;";out.startIndex="22";</tag></item><item>launch a thousand ships. But no great transformation came. The frog ran off to hide his shame. Bunny chased<tag>out.annotate="action=scene_26;action=scene_27;action=scene_28;";out.startIndex="22";</tag></item><item>launch a thousand ships. But no great transformation came. The frog ran off to hide his shame. Bunny chased in<tag>out.annotate="action=scene_26;action=scene_27;action=scene_28;";out.startIndex="22";</tag></item><item>launch a thousand ships. But no great transformation came. The frog ran off to hide his shame. Bunny chased in hot<tag>out.annotate="action=scene_26;action=scene_27;action=scene_28;";out.startIndex="22";</tag></item><item>launch a thousand ships. But no great transformation came. The frog ran off to hide his shame. Bunny chased in hot pursuit.<tag>out.annotate="action=scene_26;action=scene_27;action=scene_28;";out.startIndex="22";</tag></item><item>launch a thousand ships. But no great transformation came. The frog ran off to hide his shame. Bunny chased in hot pursuit. Don't<tag>out.annotate="action=scene_26;action=scene_27;action=scene_28;";out.startIndex="22";</tag></item><item>launch a thousand ships. But no great transformation came. The frog ran off to hide his shame. Bunny chased in hot pursuit. Don't be<tag>out.annotate="action=scene_26;action=scene_27;action=scene_28;";out.startIndex="22";</tag></item><item>launch a thousand ships. But no great transformation came. The frog ran off to hide his shame. Bunny chased in hot pursuit. Don't be an<tag>out.annotate="action=scene_26;action=scene_27;action=scene_28;";out.startIndex="22";</tag></item><item>launch a thousand ships. But no great transformation came. The frog ran off to hide his shame. Bunny chased in hot pursuit. Don't be an ungrateful<tag>out.annotate="action=scene_26;action=scene_27;action=scene_28;";out.startIndex="22";</tag></item><item>launch a thousand ships. But no great transformation came. The frog ran off to hide his shame. Bunny chased in hot pursuit. Don't be an ungrateful brute!<tag>out.annotate="action=scene_26;action=scene_27;action=scene_28;";out.startIndex="22";</tag></item><item>launch a thousand ships. But no great transformation came. The frog ran off to hide his shame. Bunny chased in hot pursuit. Don't be an ungrateful brute! Toni<tag>out.annotate="action=scene_26;action=scene_27;action=scene_28;action=scene_29;";out.startIndex="22";</tag></item><item>launch a thousand ships. But no great transformation came. The frog ran off to hide his shame. Bunny chased in hot pursuit. Don't be an ungrateful brute! Toni kissed<tag>out.annotate="action=scene_26;action=scene_27;action=scene_28;action=scene_29;";out.startIndex="22";</tag></item><item>launch a thousand ships. But no great transformation came. The frog ran off to hide his shame. Bunny chased in hot pursuit. Don't be an ungrateful brute! Toni kissed you<tag>out.annotate="action=scene_26;action=scene_27;action=scene_28;action=scene_29;";out.startIndex="22";</tag></item></one-of></rule></grammar>