<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><grammar xml:lang="en-US" root="index_43" tag-format="semantics/1.0" version="1.0" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2001/06/grammar"><rule id="index_43"><one-of><item>pursuit.<tag>out.annotate="";out.startIndex="43";</tag></item><item>pursuit. Don't<tag>out.annotate="";out.startIndex="43";</tag></item><item>pursuit. Don't be<tag>out.annotate="";out.startIndex="43";</tag></item><item>pursuit. Don't be an<tag>out.annotate="";out.startIndex="43";</tag></item><item>pursuit. Don't be an ungrateful<tag>out.annotate="";out.startIndex="43";</tag></item><item>pursuit. Don't be an ungrateful brute!<tag>out.annotate="";out.startIndex="43";</tag></item><item>pursuit. Don't be an ungrateful brute! Toni<tag>out.annotate="action=scene_29;";out.startIndex="43";</tag></item><item>pursuit. Don't be an ungrateful brute! Toni kissed<tag>out.annotate="action=scene_29;";out.startIndex="43";</tag></item><item>pursuit. Don't be an ungrateful brute! Toni kissed you<tag>out.annotate="action=scene_29;";out.startIndex="43";</tag></item><item>pursuit. Don't be an ungrateful brute! Toni kissed you when<tag>out.annotate="action=scene_29;";out.startIndex="43";</tag></item><item>pursuit. Don't be an ungrateful brute! Toni kissed you when we<tag>out.annotate="action=scene_29;";out.startIndex="43";</tag></item><item>pursuit. Don't be an ungrateful brute! Toni kissed you when we met,<tag>out.annotate="action=scene_29;";out.startIndex="43";</tag></item><item>pursuit. Don't be an ungrateful brute! Toni kissed you when we met, And<tag>out.annotate="action=scene_29;action=scene_30;";out.startIndex="43";</tag></item><item>pursuit. Don't be an ungrateful brute! Toni kissed you when we met, And tried<tag>out.annotate="action=scene_29;action=scene_30;";out.startIndex="43";</tag></item><item>pursuit. Don't be an ungrateful brute! Toni kissed you when we met, And tried to<tag>out.annotate="action=scene_29;action=scene_30;";out.startIndex="43";</tag></item><item>pursuit. Don't be an ungrateful brute! Toni kissed you when we met, And tried to make<tag>out.annotate="action=scene_29;action=scene_30;";out.startIndex="43";</tag></item><item>pursuit. Don't be an ungrateful brute! Toni kissed you when we met, And tried to make your<tag>out.annotate="action=scene_29;action=scene_30;";out.startIndex="43";</tag></item><item>pursuit. Don't be an ungrateful brute! Toni kissed you when we met, And tried to make your dreams<tag>out.annotate="action=scene_29;action=scene_30;";out.startIndex="43";</tag></item><item>pursuit. Don't be an ungrateful brute! Toni kissed you when we met, And tried to make your dreams come<tag>out.annotate="action=scene_29;action=scene_30;";out.startIndex="43";</tag></item><item>pursuit. Don't be an ungrateful brute! Toni kissed you when we met, And tried to make your dreams come true.<tag>out.annotate="action=scene_29;action=scene_30;";out.startIndex="43";</tag></item><item>pursuit. Don't be an ungrateful brute! Toni kissed you when we met, And tried to make your dreams come true. Doesn't<tag>out.annotate="action=scene_29;action=scene_30;action=scene_31;";out.startIndex="43";</tag></item><item>pursuit. Don't be an ungrateful brute! Toni kissed you when we met, And tried to make your dreams come true. Doesn't that<tag>out.annotate="action=scene_29;action=scene_30;action=scene_31;";out.startIndex="43";</tag></item><item>pursuit. Don't be an ungrateful brute! Toni kissed you when we met, And tried to make your dreams come true. Doesn't that make<tag>out.annotate="action=scene_29;action=scene_30;action=scene_31;";out.startIndex="43";</tag></item><item>pursuit. Don't be an ungrateful brute! Toni kissed you when we met, And tried to make your dreams come true. Doesn't that make you<tag>out.annotate="action=scene_29;action=scene_30;action=scene_31;";out.startIndex="43";</tag></item><item>pursuit. Don't be an ungrateful brute! Toni kissed you when we met, And tried to make your dreams come true. Doesn't that make you feel<tag>out.annotate="action=scene_29;action=scene_30;action=scene_31;";out.startIndex="43";</tag></item><item>pursuit. Don't be an ungrateful brute! Toni kissed you when we met, And tried to make your dreams come true. Doesn't that make you feel proud,<tag>out.annotate="action=scene_29;action=scene_30;action=scene_31;";out.startIndex="43";</tag></item><item>pursuit. Don't be an ungrateful brute! Toni kissed you when we met, And tried to make your dreams come true. Doesn't that make you feel proud, and<tag>out.annotate="action=scene_29;action=scene_30;action=scene_31;action=scene_32;";out.startIndex="43";</tag></item><item>pursuit. Don't be an ungrateful brute! Toni kissed you when we met, And tried to make your dreams come true. Doesn't that make you feel proud, and even<tag>out.annotate="action=scene_29;action=scene_30;action=scene_31;action=scene_32;";out.startIndex="43";</tag></item><item>pursuit. Don't be an ungrateful brute! Toni kissed you when we met, And tried to make your dreams come true. Doesn't that make you feel proud, and even somewhat<tag>out.annotate="action=scene_29;action=scene_30;action=scene_31;action=scene_32;";out.startIndex="43";</tag></item><item>pursuit. Don't be an ungrateful brute! Toni kissed you when we met, And tried to make your dreams come true. Doesn't that make you feel proud, and even somewhat thankful<tag>out.annotate="action=scene_29;action=scene_30;action=scene_31;action=scene_32;";out.startIndex="43";</tag></item></one-of></rule></grammar>